(Raj:)Please, sit.
(Raj:)I got you a cappuccino.
I remembered it was your favourite.
(Raj:)I also got crumb cake,
but remembered
it was my favourite, and I ate it.
Anyway, how are you?
(Lucy:)I'm pretty good.
(Lucy:)Listen, I just wanted to apologize
(Lucy:)for breaking up with you
in an e-mail.
(Raj:)And I ate all the crumb cake.
We both made mistakes.
(Leonard:)Okay.
(Raj:)I'm so happy you asked me here,
(Raj:)and I hope we can hang out
again sometime.
(Raj:)You know, as friends,
lovemaking partners, whatever.
(Leonard:)Oh...
(Lucy:)I'm kind of seeing someone.
(Raj:)I think I know the answer to this,
(Raj:)but just to be clear,
it's not me, right?
This is all your fault!
(Raj:)I should've listened to Mun-Mun
because I've been playing
with a cobra and her name is Penny!
(Raj:)Why are you so cruel?
Do you enjoy my pain?
(Penny:)There's a girl at the Cheesecake
Factory I can set you up with.